# ruff: noqa: B018
{
    "name": "Irregular Verb PT ğŸ‡µğŸ‡¹ / EN ğŸ‡¬ğŸ‡§",
    "description": "Creates a card for each conjugation of the verb and their reverse. Generates 10 cards.",
    "form": """
        <label for='pt_inf'>PT ğŸ‡µğŸ‡¹ Infinitive</label>
        <input type='text' name='pt_inf' value='{{ pt_inf }}'>

        <label for='eng_inf'>EN ğŸ‡¬ğŸ‡§ Infinitive</label>
        <input type='text' name='eng_inf' value='{{ eng_inf }}'>

        <label for='I'>ğŸ‡¬ğŸ‡§ I..</label>
        <input type='text' name='I' value='{{ I }}'>

        <label for='you'>ğŸ‡¬ğŸ‡§ You..</label>
        <input type='text' name='you' value='{{ you }}'>

        <label for='he'>ğŸ‡¬ğŸ‡§ He/She..</label>
        <input type='text' name='he' value='{{ he }}'>

        <label for='eu'>ğŸ‡µğŸ‡¹ Eu..</label>
        <input type='text' name='eu' value='{{ eu }}'>

        <label for='tu'>ğŸ‡µğŸ‡¹ Tu...</label>
        <input type='text' name='tu' value='{{ tu }}'>

        <label for='ele'>ğŸ‡µğŸ‡¹ VocÃª/Ele/Ela</label>
        <input type='text' name='ele' value='{{ ele }}'>

        <label for='nos'>ğŸ‡µğŸ‡¹ NÃ³s</label>
        <input type='text' name='nos' value='{{ nos }}'>

        <label for='eles'>ğŸ‡µğŸ‡¹ VocÃªs/Eles/Elas</label>
        <input type='text' name='eles'  value='{{ eles }}'>
        """,
    "preview": "ğŸ‡µğŸ‡¹ {{ pt_inf }} / ğŸ‡¬ğŸ‡§ {{ eng_inf }}",
    "cards": {
        "eu": {"question": "ğŸ‡µğŸ‡¹ --> ğŸ‡¬ğŸ‡§<br> {{ eu }}", "answer": "I {{ I }}"},
        "tu": {"question": "ğŸ‡µğŸ‡¹ --> ğŸ‡¬ğŸ‡§<br> {{ tu }}", "answer": "You {{ you }}"},
        "ele": {"question": "ğŸ‡µğŸ‡¹ --> ğŸ‡¬ğŸ‡§<br> {{ ele }}", "answer": "He/She {{ he }}"},
        "nos": {"question": "ğŸ‡µğŸ‡¹ --> ğŸ‡¬ğŸ‡§<br> {{ nos }}", "answer": "We {{ you }}"},
        "eles": {"question": "ğŸ‡µğŸ‡¹ --> ğŸ‡¬ğŸ‡§<br> {{ eles }}", "answer": "They {{ you }}"},
        "I": {"question": "ğŸ‡¬ğŸ‡§ --> ğŸ‡µğŸ‡¹<br> I {{ I }}", "answer": "{{ eu }}"},
        "you": {"question": "ğŸ‡¬ğŸ‡§ --> ğŸ‡µğŸ‡¹<br> You {{ you }}", "answer": "{{ tu }}"},
        "he": {"question": "ğŸ‡¬ğŸ‡§ --> ğŸ‡µğŸ‡¹<br> He/She {{ he }}", "answer": "{{ ele }}"},
        "we": {"question": "ğŸ‡¬ğŸ‡§ --> ğŸ‡µğŸ‡¹<br> We {{ you }}", "answer": "{{ nos }}"},
        "they": {"question": "ğŸ‡¬ğŸ‡§ --> ğŸ‡µğŸ‡¹<br> They {{ you }}", "answer": "{{ eles }}"},
    },
}


{
    "name": "Irregular Verb PT ğŸ‡µğŸ‡¹ / IT ğŸ‡®ğŸ‡¹",
    "description": "The same card and its reverse is rendered with a random conjugation of the verb. Produces 2 cards.",
    "form": """
        <label for='pt_inf'>PT ğŸ‡µğŸ‡¹ Infinitive</label>
        <input type='text' name='pt_inf' value='{{ pt_inf }}'>

        <label for='it_inf'>IT ğŸ‡®ğŸ‡¹ Infinitive</label>
        <input type='text' name='it_inf' value='{{ it_inf }}'>

        <label for='io'>ğŸ‡®ğŸ‡¹ Io..</label>
        <input type='text' name='io' value='{{ io }}'>

        <label for='tu_it'>ğŸ‡®ğŸ‡¹ Tu..</label>
        <input type='text' name='tu_it' value='{{ tu_it }}'>

        <label for='lui'>ğŸ‡®ğŸ‡¹ Lui/Lei..</label>
        <input type='text' name='lui' value='{{ lui }}'>

        <label for='noi'>ğŸ‡®ğŸ‡¹ Noi..</label>
        <input type='text' name='noi' value='{{ noi }}'>

        <label for='loro'>ğŸ‡®ğŸ‡¹ Loro..</label>
        <input type='text' name='loro' value='{{ loro }}'>

        <label for='eu'>ğŸ‡µğŸ‡¹ Eu..</label>
        <input type='text' name='eu' value='{{ eu }}'>

        <label for='tu_pt'>ğŸ‡µğŸ‡¹ Tu...</label>
        <input type='text' name='tu_pt' value='{{ tu_pt }}'>

        <label for='ele'>ğŸ‡µğŸ‡¹ VocÃª/Ele/Ela</label>
        <input type='text' name='ele' value='{{ ele }}'>

        <label for='nos'>ğŸ‡µğŸ‡¹ NÃ³s</label>
        <input type='text' name='nos' value='{{ nos }}'>

        <label for='eles'>ğŸ‡µğŸ‡¹ VocÃªs/Eles/Elas</label>
        <input type='text' name='eles'  value='{{ eles }}'>
    """,
    "preview": "ğŸ‡µğŸ‡¹ {{ pt_inf }} / ğŸ‡®ğŸ‡¹ {{ it_inf }}",
    "cards": {
        "eu": {"question": "ğŸ‡µğŸ‡¹ --> ğŸ‡®ğŸ‡¹<br> {{ eu }}", "answer": "{{ io }}"},
        "tu_pt": {"question": "ğŸ‡µğŸ‡¹ --> ğŸ‡®ğŸ‡¹<br> {{ tu_pt }}", "answer": "{{ tu_it }}"},
        "ele": {"question": "ğŸ‡µğŸ‡¹ --> ğŸ‡®ğŸ‡¹<br> {{ ele }}", "answer": "{{ lui }}"},
        "nos": {"question": "ğŸ‡µğŸ‡¹ --> ğŸ‡®ğŸ‡¹<br> {{ nos }}", "answer": "{{ noi }}"},
        "eles": {"question": "ğŸ‡µğŸ‡¹ --> ğŸ‡®ğŸ‡¹<br> {{ eles }}", "answer": "{{ loro }}"},
        "io": {"question": "ğŸ‡®ğŸ‡¹ --> ğŸ‡µğŸ‡¹<br> {{ io }}", "answer": "{{ eu }}"},
        "tu_it": {"question": "ğŸ‡®ğŸ‡¹ --> ğŸ‡µğŸ‡¹<br> {{ tu_it }}", "answer": "{{ tu_pt }}"},
        "lui": {"question": "ğŸ‡®ğŸ‡¹ --> ğŸ‡µğŸ‡¹<br> {{ lui }}", "answer": "{{ ele }}"},
        "noi": {"question": "ğŸ‡®ğŸ‡¹ --> ğŸ‡µğŸ‡¹<br> {{ noi }}", "answer": "{{ nos }}"},
        "loro": {"question": "ğŸ‡®ğŸ‡¹ --> ğŸ‡µğŸ‡¹<br> {{ loro }}", "answer": "{{ eles }}"},
    },
}
